

ABOUT ME

I have been passionate about computer science and computers since my early years. Over the past two years, I have been intensively delving into the intricacies of programming, focusing mainly on creating websites and web applications.

In 2023, I also started part-time studies. Balancing work with studies, after the first semester, I was awarded a full scholarship for top-performing students.

PROGRAMING SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT

DATABASES

• MySQL;

- TypeScript
- TypeScript
- Noue.js
- React;
- Express;

OTHERS

- RestAPI
- C#·
- NPM;
- 141 171,
- CSS;
- Tailwind
- HTML:
- JEST Test

SKILLS

- High resistance to stress;
- High creativity and innovation:
- Willingness to learn and selfdevelopment:
- Can-do attitude;
- Good manners;
- Excellent time management;
- Work under time pressure;

LANGUAGES

- Polish native;
- English level B2 FCE Cambridge English certificate;
- German basic

Grzegorz Terenda

Software Engineer

609 070 858



EDUCATION

Computer Science

WSB Merito | October 2023 - present

• Part-time first degree - Engineering degree

Geology

University of Adam Mickiewicz in Poznan | October 2014 - September 2020

- First degree studies, Geology with elements of geotechnics.

 Obtained title Engineer.
- Master degree studies, Geology.
 Obtained title Master of Geology.

EXPERIENCE

Geoprofil

Senior geologist, documenter | July 2020 - present

- interpretation of research results;
- preparation of geological and geotechnical documentation;
- preparation and interpretation of laboratory tests;
- · supervision of geological works;
- · contact with the designer.

Geoprojekt

Geologist | February 2019 - July 2020

- · Geological drilling;
- performing dynamic and static probe;
- · geotechnical construction services.

COURSES

Z2JUNIOR

Frontend online course | February 2024

- Improving knowledge of HTML, CSS and Javascript;
- Working with the frontend using the React library.
- Creating responsive websites;

MegaK

Online course on backend development | September 2022-January 2023

- Creating a backend using the Node.js environment and the Express.js framework;
- Learning about relational (SQL) and non-relational databases (MongoDB);
- · Use of Git version control;
- · Creating REST APIs;
- · React library basics;
- · Writing unit tests using Jest.